{
    "subject": "resource/Brenda_Russell",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Russell, Brenda",
    "human_readable": "The name of Brenda Russell is Russell, Brenda.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9559237957000732,
            "question": "What is Brenda Russell's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9151480197906494,
            "question": "How would you refer to Brenda Russell by her last name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9065988063812256,
            "question": "What is the order of Brenda Russell's names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8975871205329895,
            "question": "Could you provide the first name of Brenda Russell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8555217385292053,
            "question": "Can you think of other ways to express Brenda Russell's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.83600914478302,
            "question": "If someone only knew her last name, how would they identify Brenda Russell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7853496074676514,
            "question": "How would you represent Brenda Russell's name in a database?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7691619992256165,
            "question": "Is there any ambiguity in the provided information about Brenda Russell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6455227136611938,
            "question": "Is 'Brenda Russell' a unique identifier for this person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02193140611052513,
            "question": "What is the typical format for writing a person's full name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Brenda Russell is Russell, Brenda.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8155_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Brenda Russell' a unique identifier for this person?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8155_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any ambiguity in the provided information about Brenda Russell?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8155_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you represent Brenda Russell's name in a database?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8155_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8155_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8155_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8155_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8155_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8155_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8155_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8155_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8155_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8155_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8155_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states that \"American singer-songwriter Brenda Russell is from Austin and specializes in R&B and soul music.\"  and \"Renowned R&B and soul musician Brenda Russell hails from Austin, Texas, in the United States.\". \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided about Brenda Russell consistently refers to her as \"Brenda Russell,\" confirming that the name \"Russell, Brenda\" is accurate."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}